<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Travels on Carry On Round The World</title>
    <link>/travels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Travels on Carry On Round The World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 20:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/travels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SOBO PCT Hike 2019</title>
      <link>/travels/sobo-pct-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 17:43:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/sobo-pct-2019/</guid>
      <description>In January of 2019, while we were chilling in Kampot, Cambodia, we were trying to figure out what we would for the summer of 2019. Eventually we decided that we wanted to hike the Pacific Crest Trail (PCT) from the Canadian border in Washington to the Mexican border near San Diego. So using our phones at 3AM in Cambodia we jumped online for the second permit lottery and got 2 permits for northbound PCT hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia</title>
      <link>/travels/malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 15:49:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/malaysia/</guid>
      <description>We had decided to head to Malaysia next, giving ourselves about a month before heading to Lipe. We went from Phnom Penh to Kuala Lumpur on Air Asia, it was a short flight. The airport in KL is massive but modern and we moved through everything quickly. We got sims and a Grab Taxi to downtown KL.
We booked a suite at Mercu Summer Suites, which are 99% AirBnb’s. It was a great location, close enough to get places by walking or Grab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam</title>
      <link>/travels/vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 21:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/vietnam/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
Our next stop was Vietnam… well, with a stop in Bangkok to get our Vietnamese visas. We decided to stay at the Vie again, partly because it was central to everywhere we needed to go and we deserved to be spoiled after Nepal! We were also able to spend an evening with Ben since he lived close enough to come into the area.
Ha Noi We arrived in Ha Noi on a Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nepal in Fall</title>
      <link>/travels/nepal-in-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/nepal-in-fall/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
On our way to Nepal, yes we are going back to hike the Annapurna Circuit again, we decided to take a couple of days and spoil ourselves in Bangkok. We stayed at our favorite hotel, the Vie, pigged out on breakfast buffets, sushi and curries, did some shopping and slept.
We arrived in Kathmandu and headed back to Hotel Yala Peak for two nights. We went and got our permits and got organized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka</title>
      <link>/travels/sri-lanka/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 07:18:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/sri-lanka/</guid>
      <description>Sri Lanka! It wasn&amp;rsquo;t originally on our radar but our friends, Judy and Carl, had raved about their experience there so we thought hmmm&amp;hellip; why not? Plus the photos they had sent made it look really good and they were able to give us some great ideas on places to go. We&amp;rsquo;d spent the summer back in Canada after coming home from 18 months of travel.
The Flights John and Rita dropped us off at the Cranbrook Airport so we could start our journey to Sri Lanka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creston Summer 2018</title>
      <link>/travels/creston-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 12:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/creston-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>There was a delay in getting our flight out of Kathmandhu, which isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual apparently, but about an hour later, we were able to board the Air China flight to Chengdu. There were only 3 people in the business class area so we had room to spread out. We still think the co-pilot was also handling service but could be wrong. The flight was smooth and we landed in China! We had to get on a bus and were driven to the terminal, we were only transit passengers so expected to just go to the next gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nepal in Spring</title>
      <link>/travels/nepal-in-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 19:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/nepal-in-spring/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
Bangkok After an early morning departure from our Taipei AirBnB, we were outside waiting for the cab at 4:30 am. We are headed to Nepal with an over night in Bangkok. We decided to spoil ourselves and booked The Vie in Bangkok and even better, breakfast at The Vie. We spent the afternoon in Bangkok looking for gear for Nepal and going to a movie (Black Panther, meh&amp;hellip;). After a nice supper at Muay Thai we headed back to pack and relax at our room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei</title>
      <link>/travels/taipei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 19:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/taipei/</guid>
      <description>After the Philippines, we decided to do a stop in the Taiwan. A good friend of Helen&amp;rsquo;s is from there and we know several people who really enjoyed it. We managed to get a good flight from Cebu, to Manila to Taipei on EVA air so off we went. We did have a little hitch thinking the flight departed Manila from the same terminal we arrived to from Cebu. Unfortunately not the case and after 20 minutes trying to figure it out we realized we had to head to terminal 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippines</title>
      <link>/travels/philippines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 17:33:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/philippines/</guid>
      <description>Cebu Photo Album
We decided after all our driving around in Oz and NZ, that we needed some beach time. We&amp;rsquo;d heard so many awesome things and seen great photos so decided the Philippines was the next stop and used some of our precious mileage points to fly business class to Manila from Auckland. After some research, we didn&amp;rsquo;t even leave the airport in Manila as it is supposedly a sketchy shithole, and just headed over to get a flight to Cebu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand North Island</title>
      <link>/travels/new-zealand-north-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 17:33:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/new-zealand-north-island/</guid>
      <description>The Ferry We had booked in advance to get the ferry so with tickets in hand we headed over at the recommended time, strangely we were some of the first people there. I needed coffee but Paul didn&amp;rsquo;t want one so I ran into a little trouble when I went to order. I only brought my credit card and needed to have a minimum purchase to use it at the coffee place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand South Island</title>
      <link>/travels/new-zealand-south-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 17:33:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/new-zealand-south-island/</guid>
      <description>When we were in Australia, hiding from the rain for a couple of days in Alva Beach, we organized Tasmania and determined our next stop should be New Zealand. We organized flights with Jet Star and rented an older camper van from CampaSouth. We were able to fly from Hobart to Christchurch, with a short stopover in Melbourne. We had some issues in Melbourne, going from the domestic terminal to international isn&amp;rsquo;t a long walk but was very challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasmania</title>
      <link>/travels/tasmania/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 12:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/tasmania/</guid>
      <description>10 days in Tasmania wasn’t enough. We could of easily spent at least a couple more weeks to explore this lovely island but we only had a short time left on our Ozzy visas. It remains one of our favorite places… even though we landed during a massive rain storm and spent the day hunkered in the van. 🙂
Hobart Area: We arrived here quite early and went to get our next van from Tassie Motor Shacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Daintree to Melbourne</title>
      <link>/travels/australia-daintree-to-melbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 17:32:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/australia-daintree-to-melbourne/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
Australia Part 2 was us heading back south from the Daintree down to Melbourne and beyond. The original plan was to head back inland but we ended up going back along the coast. The reasons… a random message allowed us to reconnect with some of our favorite people and why not? We really enjoyed some of the places on the way up. Plus we needed to test out the Zombie Apocalypse machine that we saw on the way up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia: Brisbane to Daintree</title>
      <link>/travels/australia-brisbane-to-daintree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 09:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/australia-brisbane-to-daintree/</guid>
      <description>The land of OZ, the land of OZ! Okay, the land of Australia but still awesome! While spending 2 months in Kampot we were lucky enough to borrow a computer to figure out what to do next. The original plan was Vietnam, but the weather there wasn’t co-operating. So how about a complete change of scenery and we look into renting a camper van and travel Eastern Australia! Flights, check, Phnom Penh to Brisbane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Months in Kampot</title>
      <link>/travels/2-months-in-kampot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:30:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/2-months-in-kampot/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
After a whirlwind trip to Hong Kong, we headed back to Cambodia for further adventures. We had an overnight in Phnom Penh before heading south to Kampot to visit our old friend Lee. We ended up staying there for 2 months… yep, 2 months in Kampot.
Bokor If you are in Kampot you have to go up Bokor mountain. It’s spooky, beautiful and weird all at the same time and has its own weather system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong? What!?!</title>
      <link>/travels/hong-kong-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 13:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/hong-kong-what/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong? What!?! That was unplanned… well yes, but everything has pretty much been unplanned! Let’s make a long story short… in May we looked into getting tickets to the Liverpool FC preseason game in July at Hong Kong Stadium. They sold out in less than 24 hrs… too bad, moved on. While in Don Det, Laos, we discovered that one of Paul’s favorite Liverpool podcasts, The Anfield Wrap, was going to do a live show at the Hong Kong game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/travels/cambodia-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 07:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/cambodia-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Cambodia (Part 1)? What? Why, you ask? Even if you didn’t, I’m pretending you did so I can tell you all about it! After a great time on the 4000 islands in Laos our next stop was Cambodia. We were very excited for a couple of reasons the main one being an opportunity to see our old friend Lee. We hadn’t seen him in years… basically since he moved there from Calgary, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land of Laos</title>
      <link>/travels/the-land-of-laos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 17:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/the-land-of-laos/</guid>
      <description>The Land of Laos was next on our list. We met wonderful people, saw some beautiful sites and had a blast. We spent the most time in Luang Prebang, Vang Vieng and the 4000 Islands.
Slow Boat on the Mekong to Luang Prabang Photo Album
This is a two day journey with an overnight in Pak Beng where we stayed at the Monsavanh Guesthouse. We crossed over the Mekong on the Friendhsip bridge which is the the border at Chiang Khong into Laos and then took a minibus to the slow boats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Thailand</title>
      <link>/travels/northern-thailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 20:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/northern-thailand/</guid>
      <description>After Myanmar we spent several weeks in Northern Thailand. All the Chiang’s together: Chiang Mai, Chiang Dao, Chiang Rai and Chiang Khong!
Chiang Mai Photo Album
We decided to get organized in Chiang Mai. Mailed some items back that we don’t use, saw Wonder Woman and did a cooking class with Pat and Liz. I’d wanted to a do a class so this was more for me then Paul. We got to make several dishes and no injuries occured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar</title>
      <link>/travels/myanmar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:26:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/myanmar/</guid>
      <description>After 60+ days in Thailand we headed to Myanmar for a new adventure. We woke up early and headed to the green bus depot to take us to Mae Sot on the border. We stayed one night at a nice little place called Phanu Guesthouse.
Hpa-An Hpa-An Photo Album
First stop Myawaddy, right across the border from Mae Sot. We were helped by “Mike” and were soon sharing a taxi with Karen, nurse from USA who was volunteering in Thailand at the Burmese border during her retirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coles Notes</title>
      <link>/travels/coles-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:26:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/coles-notes/</guid>
      <description>On Facebook, you may have been exposed to our constant updates and many temple and/or Pagoda photos. For those not on Facebook or who have blocked us after being fed up with the aforementioned pagodas… here is the Cole’s notes version of our first couple of months:
Koh Lipe – March 2017 Photo Album
This time we stayed at The Reef instead of our usual Andaman Resort, which was taken over by new owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE Asia on Our Way</title>
      <link>/travels/se-asia-on-our-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 08:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/se-asia-on-our-way/</guid>
      <description>After some very crazy, hectic, emotional weeks we are on our way. We left on the first leg of our adventure on February 28, 2017! Before I get into too much, we need to send a big thank you to Paul’s Mom and Dad. We wouldn’t have made it through the last weekend without their help. Between letting us store things, taking care of our mail and our car (VW TDI to be returned), helping us pack up and clean the apartment and taking us to the airport… well needless to say we got it all done and I was even able to spend several hours with my Mom the day before we left with no stress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>