<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Travels on Carry On Round The World</title>
    <link>/travels/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Travels on Carry On Round The World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 20:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/travels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SOBO PCT Hike 2019</title>
      <link>/travels/sobo-pct-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 17:43:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/sobo-pct-2019/</guid>
      <description>In January of 2019, while we were chilling in Kampot, Cambodia, we were trying to figure out what we would for the summer of 2019. Eventually we decided that we wanted to hike the Pacific Crest Trail (PCT) from the Canadian border in Washington to the Mexican border near San Diego. So using our phones at 3AM in Cambodia we jumped online for the second permit lottery and got 2 permits for northbound PCT hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creston Summer 2018</title>
      <link>/travels/creston-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 12:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/creston-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>There was a delay in getting our flight out of Kathmandhu, which isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual apparently, but about an hour later, we were able to board the Air China flight to Chengdu. There were only 3 people in the business class area so we had room to spread out. We still think the co-pilot was also handling service but could be wrong. The flight was smooth and we landed in China! We had to get on a bus and were driven to the terminal, we were only transit passengers so expected to just go to the next gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia: Brisbane to Daintree</title>
      <link>/travels/australia-brisbane-to-daintree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 09:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/australia-brisbane-to-daintree/</guid>
      <description>The land of OZ, the land of OZ! Okay, the land of Australia but still awesome! While spending 2 months in Kampot we were lucky enough to borrow a computer to figure out what to do next. The original plan was Vietnam, but the weather there wasn’t co-operating. So how about a complete change of scenery and we look into renting a camper van and travel Eastern Australia! Flights, check, Phnom Penh to Brisbane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Months in Kampot</title>
      <link>/travels/2-months-in-kampot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:30:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/2-months-in-kampot/</guid>
      <description>After a whirlwind trip to Hong Kong, we headed back to Cambodia for further adventures. We had an overnight in Phnom Penh before heading south to Kampot to visit our old friend Lee. We ended up staying there for 2 months… yep, 2 months in Kampot.
Bokor If you are in Kampot you have to go up Bokor mountain. It’s spooky, beautiful and weird all at the same time and has its own weather system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong? What!?!</title>
      <link>/travels/hong-kong-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 13:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/hong-kong-what/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong? What!?! That was unplanned… well yes, but everything has pretty much been unplanned! Let’s make a long story short… in May we looked into getting tickets to the Liverpool FC preseason game in July at Hong Kong Stadium. They sold out in less than 24 hrs… too bad, moved on. While in Don Det, Laos, we discovered that one of Paul’s favorite podcasts was going to do a live show at the Hong Kong game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/travels/cambodia-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 07:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/cambodia-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Cambodia (Part 1)? What? Why, you ask? Even if you didn’t, I’m pretending you did so I can tell you all about it! After a great time on the 4000 islands in Laos our next stop was Cambodia. We were very excited for a couple of reasons the main one being an opportunity to see our old friend Lee. We hadn’t seen him in years… basically since he moved there from Calgary, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land of Laos</title>
      <link>/travels/the-land-of-laos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 17:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/the-land-of-laos/</guid>
      <description>The Land of Laos was next on our list. We met wonderful people, saw some beautiful sites and had a blast. We spent the most time in Luang Prebang, Vang Vieng and the 4000 Islands.
Photo Album: Slow Boat on the Mekong to Luang Prabang This is a two day journey with an overnight in Pakbeng at the Monsavanh Guesthouse. We crossed the border at Chiang Khong into Laos and then took a minibus to the slow boats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Thailand</title>
      <link>/travels/northern-thailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 20:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/northern-thailand/</guid>
      <description>After Myanmar we spent several weeks in Northern Thailand. All the Chiang’s together: Chiang Mai, Chiang Dao, Chiang Rai and Chiang Khong!
Chiang Mai We decided to get organized in Chiang Mai. Mailed some items back that we don’t use, saw Wonder Woman and did a cooking class with Pat and Liz. I’d wanted to a do a class so this was more for me then Paul. We got to make several dishes and no injuries occured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar</title>
      <link>/travels/myanmar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:26:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/myanmar/</guid>
      <description>After 60+ days in Thailand we headed to Myanmar for a new adventure. We woke up early and headed to the green bus depot to take us to Mae Sot on the border. We stayed one night at a nice little place called Phanu Guesthouse.
Hpa-An Hpa-An Photo Album
First stop Myawaddy, right across the border from Mae Sot. We were helped by “Mike” and were soon sharing a taxi with Karen, nurse from USA who was volunteering in Thailand at the Burmese border during her retirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coles Notes</title>
      <link>/travels/coles-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:26:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/coles-notes/</guid>
      <description>On Facebook, you may have been exposed to our constant updates and many temple and/or Pagoda photos. For those not on Facebook or who have blocked us after being fed up with the aforementioned pagodas… here is the Cole’s notes version of our first couple of months:
Photo Album: Koh Lipe – March 2017
This time we stayed at The Reef instead of our usual Andaman Resort, which was taken over by new owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE Asia on Our Way</title>
      <link>/travels/se-asia-on-our-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 08:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/se-asia-on-our-way/</guid>
      <description>After some very crazy, hectic, emotional weeks we are on our way. We left on the first leg of our adventure on February 28, 2017! Before I get into too much, we need to send a big thank you to Paul’s Mom and Dad. We wouldn’t have made it through the last weekend without their help. Between letting us store things, taking care of our mail and our car (VW TDI to be returned), helping us pack up and clean the apartment and taking us to the airport… well needless to say we got it all done and I was even able to spend several hours with my Mom the day before we left with no stress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>