<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carry On Round The World</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carry On Round The World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 18:26:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 18:26:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>So who are these people anyway? We’re a couple of desk jockeys in our forties that have decided to take the leap, re-prioritize everything and do some long-term travelling. There’s many ramifications to that last sentence. How do you go from owning everything you’ve accumulated over a lifetime and having good careers to pulling up and travelling around the world? Well, we don’t completely know yet but we are doing our best to pull it off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Diesel Heater</title>
      <link>/van-life/chinese-diesel-heater/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 16:51:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/chinese-diesel-heater/</guid>
      <description>Every Canadian Van build needs a heater at some point. We&amp;rsquo;ve been camping in the Rockies in July and August and it has snowed. After looking at all of the solutions to the heat problem, one stood out: Chinese Diesel Heaters. They are by far and away the leader in price/performance, mostly due to the exorbitant costs $1000USD+ of brand name gas, propane and diesel heaters. Our transit has a gas fuel tank already but for several hundred dollars savings we are willing to add a small diesel tank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Headliner and Thinsulate</title>
      <link>/van-life/headliner-and-thinsulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 09:14:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/headliner-and-thinsulate/</guid>
      <description>Removing the headliner makes insulating above a breeze. All you need for tools are an 7mm socket and a set of trim removal tools like this. With the following steps it only took about 10 minutes to remove and same to re-install.
  Pop out the 3 orange clips holding up the rear center of the headliner.
  Pry out and put aside 2 plastic trays in center of headliner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roof Fan Installation</title>
      <link>/van-life/roof-fan-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 15:22:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/roof-fan-installation/</guid>
      <description>A big right of passage when DIY&amp;rsquo;ing a van is the roof fan installation. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing like cutting a gaping hole in a brand new van. No pressure! 🙂 I highly recommend you pick up a decent metal jigsaw blade. I believe the one I used was 25 teeth per inch and it cut the sheet metal like butter even with an old jigsaw. I also recommend watching as many YouTube videos as you can stomach on this as there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of good ideas (and what not to do) out there, they&amp;rsquo;re just spread out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sound Deadener and Flooring</title>
      <link>/van-life/sound-deadener-and-flooring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:17:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/sound-deadener-and-flooring/</guid>
      <description>The first thing we did to our new van was to add some Noico sound deadener to the metal panels. This stops a lot of the resonance that the larger panel sections are prone to and drastically reduces noise. We ordered 2 boxes of the 80 mil 36 sqft Noico and it worked out almost perfectly to do the walls, ceiling, above the front headliner, inside the side and rear door panels and inside the passenger seat pedestal (to help with noise from our Chinese diesel heater).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Pad</title>
      <link>/van-life/parking-pad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 10:22:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/parking-pad/</guid>
      <description>Paul&amp;rsquo;s parents have graciously offered to let us park the van at the side of their house when its not in use as we are off travelling. There was tons of room for the van and it is nicely sheltered between 2 houses. The first time we parked it there it spun out a lot as the pebbles are quite large and round making them like ball bearings. Rather than digging holes with spinning wheels and having to fill them in every time we come and go we decided to make a better parking pad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s Travel Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/paulspack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 20:41:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/paulspack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what is in Paul&amp;rsquo;s pack for travel. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see his Pacific Crest Trail load out here and his Annapurna Circuit load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen&#39;s Travel Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/helenspack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 10:41:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/helenspack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what is in Helen&amp;rsquo;s pack for travel. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see her Pacific Crest Trail load out here and her Annapurna Circuit load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOBO PCT Hike 2019</title>
      <link>/travels/sobo-pct-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 17:43:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/sobo-pct-2019/</guid>
      <description>In January of 2019, while we were chilling in Kampot, Cambodia, we were trying to figure out what we would for the summer of 2019. Eventually we decided that we wanted to hike the Pacific Crest Trail (PCT) from the Canadian border in Washington to the Mexican border near San Diego. So using our phones at 3AM in Cambodia we jumped online for the second permit lottery and got 2 permits for northbound PCT hikes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen&#39;s PCT Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/helens-pct-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:44:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/helens-pct-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Helen&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Pacific Crest Trail. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see her travel load out here and her Annapurna Circuit load out here.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s PCT Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/pauls-pct-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:44:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/pauls-pct-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Paul&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Pacific Crest Trail. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see his travel load out here and his Annapurna Circuit load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malaysia</title>
      <link>/travels/malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 15:49:36 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/malaysia/</guid>
      <description>We had decided to head to Malaysia next, giving ourselves about a month before heading to Lipe. We went from Phnom Penh to Kuala Lumpur on Air Asia, it was a short flight. The airport in KL is massive but modern and we moved through everything quickly. We got sims and a Grab Taxi to downtown KL.
We booked a suite at Mercu Summer Suites, which are 99% AirBnb’s. It was a great location, close enough to get places by walking or Grab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam</title>
      <link>/travels/vietnam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 21:34:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/vietnam/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
Our next stop was Vietnam… well, with a stop in Bangkok to get our Vietnamese visas. We decided to stay at the Vie again, partly because it was central to everywhere we needed to go and we deserved to be spoiled after Nepal! We were also able to spend an evening with Ben since he lived close enough to come into the area.
Ha Noi We arrived in Ha Noi on a Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nepal in Fall</title>
      <link>/travels/nepal-in-fall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 17:36:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/nepal-in-fall/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
On our way to Nepal, yes we are going back to hike the Annapurna Circuit again, we decided to take a couple of days and spoil ourselves in Bangkok. We stayed at our favorite hotel, the Vie, pigged out on breakfast buffets, sushi and curries, did some shopping and slept.
We arrived in Kathmandu and headed back to Hotel Yala Peak for two nights. We went and got our permits and got organized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka</title>
      <link>/travels/sri-lanka/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 07:18:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/sri-lanka/</guid>
      <description>Sri Lanka! It wasn&amp;rsquo;t originally on our radar but our friends, Judy and Carl, had raved about their experience there so we thought hmmm&amp;hellip; why not? Plus the photos they had sent made it look really good and they were able to give us some great ideas on places to go. We&amp;rsquo;d spent the summer back in Canada after coming home from 18 months of travel.
The Flights John and Rita dropped us off at the Cranbrook Airport so we could start our journey to Sri Lanka.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen&#39;s Annapurna Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/helens-annapurna-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/helens-annapurna-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Helen&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Annapurna Circuit treks. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see her travel load out here and her PCT load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s Annapurna Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/pauls-annapurna-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:43:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/pauls-annapurna-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Paul&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Annapurna Circuit treks. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see his travel load out here and his PCT load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creston Summer 2018</title>
      <link>/travels/creston-summer-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 12:35:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/creston-summer-2018/</guid>
      <description>There was a delay in getting our flight out of Kathmandhu, which isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual apparently, but about an hour later, we were able to board the Air China flight to Chengdu. There were only 3 people in the business class area so we had room to spread out. We still think the co-pilot was also handling service but could be wrong. The flight was smooth and we landed in China! We had to get on a bus and were driven to the terminal, we were only transit passengers so expected to just go to the next gate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nepal in Spring</title>
      <link>/travels/nepal-in-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 19:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/nepal-in-spring/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
Bangkok After an early morning departure from our Taipei AirBnB, we were outside waiting for the cab at 4:30 am. We are headed to Nepal with an over night in Bangkok. We decided to spoil ourselves and booked The Vie in Bangkok and even better, breakfast at The Vie. We spent the afternoon in Bangkok looking for gear for Nepal and going to a movie (Black Panther, meh&amp;hellip;). After a nice supper at Muay Thai we headed back to pack and relax at our room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taipei</title>
      <link>/travels/taipei/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 19:51:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/taipei/</guid>
      <description>After the Philippines, we decided to do a stop in the Taiwan. A good friend of Helen&amp;rsquo;s is from there and we know several people who really enjoyed it. We managed to get a good flight from Cebu, to Manila to Taipei on EVA air so off we went. We did have a little hitch thinking the flight departed Manila from the same terminal we arrived to from Cebu. Unfortunately not the case and after 20 minutes trying to figure it out we realized we had to head to terminal 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philippines</title>
      <link>/travels/philippines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 17:33:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/philippines/</guid>
      <description>Cebu Photo Album
We decided after all our driving around in Oz and NZ, that we needed some beach time. We&amp;rsquo;d heard so many awesome things and seen great photos so decided the Philippines was the next stop and used some of our precious mileage points to fly business class to Manila from Auckland. After some research, we didn&amp;rsquo;t even leave the airport in Manila as it is supposedly a sketchy shithole, and just headed over to get a flight to Cebu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand North Island</title>
      <link>/travels/new-zealand-north-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 17:33:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/new-zealand-north-island/</guid>
      <description>The Ferry We had booked in advance to get the ferry so with tickets in hand we headed over at the recommended time, strangely we were some of the first people there. I needed coffee but Paul didn&amp;rsquo;t want one so I ran into a little trouble when I went to order. I only brought my credit card and needed to have a minimum purchase to use it at the coffee place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand South Island</title>
      <link>/travels/new-zealand-south-island/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2018 17:33:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/new-zealand-south-island/</guid>
      <description>When we were in Australia, hiding from the rain for a couple of days in Alva Beach, we organized Tasmania and determined our next stop should be New Zealand. We organized flights with Jet Star and rented an older camper van from CampaSouth. We were able to fly from Hobart to Christchurch, with a short stopover in Melbourne. We had some issues in Melbourne, going from the domestic terminal to international isn&amp;rsquo;t a long walk but was very challenging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tasmania</title>
      <link>/travels/tasmania/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 12:48:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/tasmania/</guid>
      <description>10 days in Tasmania wasn’t enough. We could of easily spent at least a couple more weeks to explore this lovely island but we only had a short time left on our Ozzy visas. It remains one of our favorite places… even though we landed during a massive rain storm and spent the day hunkered in the van. 🙂
Hobart Area: We arrived here quite early and went to get our next van from Tassie Motor Shacks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia Daintree to Melbourne</title>
      <link>/travels/australia-daintree-to-melbourne/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 17:32:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/australia-daintree-to-melbourne/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
Australia Part 2 was us heading back south from the Daintree down to Melbourne and beyond. The original plan was to head back inland but we ended up going back along the coast. The reasons… a random message allowed us to reconnect with some of our favorite people and why not? We really enjoyed some of the places on the way up. Plus we needed to test out the Zombie Apocalypse machine that we saw on the way up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australia: Brisbane to Daintree</title>
      <link>/travels/australia-brisbane-to-daintree/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 09:31:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/australia-brisbane-to-daintree/</guid>
      <description>The land of OZ, the land of OZ! Okay, the land of Australia but still awesome! While spending 2 months in Kampot we were lucky enough to borrow a computer to figure out what to do next. The original plan was Vietnam, but the weather there wasn’t co-operating. So how about a complete change of scenery and we look into renting a camper van and travel Eastern Australia! Flights, check, Phnom Penh to Brisbane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Months in Kampot</title>
      <link>/travels/2-months-in-kampot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:30:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/2-months-in-kampot/</guid>
      <description>Photo Album
After a whirlwind trip to Hong Kong, we headed back to Cambodia for further adventures. We had an overnight in Phnom Penh before heading south to Kampot to visit our old friend Lee. We ended up staying there for 2 months… yep, 2 months in Kampot.
Bokor If you are in Kampot you have to go up Bokor mountain. It’s spooky, beautiful and weird all at the same time and has its own weather system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong? What!?!</title>
      <link>/travels/hong-kong-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 13:28:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/hong-kong-what/</guid>
      <description>Hong Kong? What!?! That was unplanned… well yes, but everything has pretty much been unplanned! Let’s make a long story short… in May we looked into getting tickets to the Liverpool FC preseason game in July at Hong Kong Stadium. They sold out in less than 24 hrs… too bad, moved on. While in Don Det, Laos, we discovered that one of Paul’s favorite Liverpool podcasts, The Anfield Wrap, was going to do a live show at the Hong Kong game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/travels/cambodia-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 07:28:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/cambodia-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Cambodia (Part 1)? What? Why, you ask? Even if you didn’t, I’m pretending you did so I can tell you all about it! After a great time on the 4000 islands in Laos our next stop was Cambodia. We were very excited for a couple of reasons the main one being an opportunity to see our old friend Lee. We hadn’t seen him in years… basically since he moved there from Calgary, Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Land of Laos</title>
      <link>/travels/the-land-of-laos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 17:27:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/the-land-of-laos/</guid>
      <description>The Land of Laos was next on our list. We met wonderful people, saw some beautiful sites and had a blast. We spent the most time in Luang Prebang, Vang Vieng and the 4000 Islands.
Slow Boat on the Mekong to Luang Prabang Photo Album
This is a two day journey with an overnight in Pak Beng where we stayed at the Monsavanh Guesthouse. We crossed over the Mekong on the Friendhsip bridge which is the the border at Chiang Khong into Laos and then took a minibus to the slow boats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Thailand</title>
      <link>/travels/northern-thailand/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 20:27:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/northern-thailand/</guid>
      <description>After Myanmar we spent several weeks in Northern Thailand. All the Chiang’s together: Chiang Mai, Chiang Dao, Chiang Rai and Chiang Khong!
Chiang Mai Photo Album
We decided to get organized in Chiang Mai. Mailed some items back that we don’t use, saw Wonder Woman and did a cooking class with Pat and Liz. I’d wanted to a do a class so this was more for me then Paul. We got to make several dishes and no injuries occured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar</title>
      <link>/travels/myanmar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 17:26:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/myanmar/</guid>
      <description>After 60+ days in Thailand we headed to Myanmar for a new adventure. We woke up early and headed to the green bus depot to take us to Mae Sot on the border. We stayed one night at a nice little place called Phanu Guesthouse.
Hpa-An Hpa-An Photo Album
First stop Myawaddy, right across the border from Mae Sot. We were helped by “Mike” and were soon sharing a taxi with Karen, nurse from USA who was volunteering in Thailand at the Burmese border during her retirement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coles Notes</title>
      <link>/travels/coles-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 17:26:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/coles-notes/</guid>
      <description>On Facebook, you may have been exposed to our constant updates and many temple and/or Pagoda photos. For those not on Facebook or who have blocked us after being fed up with the aforementioned pagodas… here is the Cole’s notes version of our first couple of months:
Koh Lipe – March 2017 Photo Album
This time we stayed at The Reef instead of our usual Andaman Resort, which was taken over by new owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SE Asia on Our Way</title>
      <link>/travels/se-asia-on-our-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 08:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/travels/se-asia-on-our-way/</guid>
      <description>After some very crazy, hectic, emotional weeks we are on our way. We left on the first leg of our adventure on February 28, 2017! Before I get into too much, we need to send a big thank you to Paul’s Mom and Dad. We wouldn’t have made it through the last weekend without their help. Between letting us store things, taking care of our mail and our car (VW TDI to be returned), helping us pack up and clean the apartment and taking us to the airport… well needless to say we got it all done and I was even able to spend several hours with my Mom the day before we left with no stress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Quit</title>
      <link>/articles/we-quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 15:53:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/we-quit/</guid>
      <description>We quit! Yep, we quit our jobs! February 9th, 2017 is our last day. Paul gave notice just before Christmas and I told my boss on Friday the 13th! The humour of that, while lost on some people, was not lost on me and I will admit to a giggle about it. Luckily our coworkers are very excited for us and have been great. For both of us the build up to quitting was bigger than the reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Banking for Canadians</title>
      <link>/articles/travel-banking-for-canadians/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 16:21:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/travel-banking-for-canadians/</guid>
      <description>We use different cards in Canada than when travelling. At home we’ve churned cards for Aeroplan points and used different cash back cards. This has saved us money on purchases and allowed us to build up a big pot of Aeroplan points. These will allow us to fly with points between the major regions of our upcoming RTW trip. When we are on the road though we are more concerned about the banking fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision Made Tickets Booked</title>
      <link>/articles/decision-made-tickets-booked/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/decision-made-tickets-booked/</guid>
      <description>Decision Made! What? When did this happen? I know it’s been a while since I took the time to write out something about our plans. Partially because we have been super busy and some things took much longer then expected so we weren’t sure what was happening. We also had some changes in the family that had us questioning our decisions. The quick catch up:
 June – accepted offer on the house, Paul ruptured his Achilles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning Our RTW Route</title>
      <link>/articles/planning-our-rtw-route/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 16:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/planning-our-rtw-route/</guid>
      <description>So far we’ve come up with this list of countries we’d like to see. I’m sure it will morph over time but it’s a good starting point. Planning our RTW route started out as what seemed like a massively important and overwhelming decision. After much research and brain racking we came to the conclusion that for us, it really didn’t need to be. We decided to start in Thailand, in SE Asia as we’ve been there many times and it’d let us get our traveling legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a Pack</title>
      <link>/articles/choosing-a-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 17:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/choosing-a-pack/</guid>
      <description>Expect The Unexpected Choosing a travel pack is a major decision when traveling. The wrong choice can have a big impact on a trip. Dragging a roller through sand to your beach side bungalow, carrying a duffel bag by its single carry strap for half an hour through a city or seeing your backpack come up the luggage carousel ramp with one of its shoulder straps torn off is no fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airline Carry on Rules</title>
      <link>/articles/airline-carry-on-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 17:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/airline-carry-on-rules/</guid>
      <description>Airline carry on rules can vary wildly. They each have their own specific guidelines for items that you can bring on-board a flight. Some even allow for a secondary “personal item” like a purse or laptop bag. If you do your research you’ll find lots of people saying a 45L pack is good for carry on. As you’ll find out, this is not always the case. If you aren’t exactly within an airline’s requirements it’ll come down to the whim of the staff working on the day of your flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definition of Home</title>
      <link>/articles/definition-of-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:03:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/definition-of-home/</guid>
      <description>What’s the definition of home? It sounds simple doesn’t it but I’m not sure that it is. I was born in Liverpool, England, Helen was born in Belfast, Northern Ireland. We both moved to Canada with our families. Helen at the young age of 4 and myself at 13. Years later we met in Saskatchewan in 1991 and since then have spent our last 23 years living our adult lives together in Calgary, Alberta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carry on Only</title>
      <link>/articles/carry-on-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 16:41:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/carry-on-only/</guid>
      <description>28 days later and we are back! It wasn’t years on the road but it was a good test of living out of our new Gregory 38 L and 40 L bags (J38 and Z40). The traveling with carry on only experiment was definitely a success. It sure was liberating being able to walk off the plane with all our possessions on our backs. We flew Air Canada, Thai Airways International and the regional Thai Smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moments of November Oddness</title>
      <link>/articles/moments-of-november-oddness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 17:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/moments-of-november-oddness/</guid>
      <description>Is oddness a word? Since it didn’t come up underlined I can only assume yes, I could confirm that it is.. but where is the fun in that? I like the start so will just go with it. November has been full of odd moments. It all started off when I booked a massage… sounds scary I know! It appears that the booking of the massage has resulted in me losing my job, being diagnosed with Celiac Disease, my family together for the first time in 17 years, a new hot water tank and swimming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gear Conundrum</title>
      <link>/articles/the-gear-conundrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 18:10:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/the-gear-conundrum/</guid>
      <description>Winter is coming… no really it is supposed to snow. Thankfully we have restored the garage to its intended use and our vehicles are parked indoors so we won’t need to get our the ice scraper in the morning. After a recent work trip to Chicago by me, we were able to update our countries with carry on only to include the US. I have to admit I was somewhat nervous about doing carry on with just me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling Everything to Travel</title>
      <link>/articles/selling-everything-to-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 18:26:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/selling-everything-to-travel/</guid>
      <description>What!?! This was supposed to be easy.. sell everything and travel. Sure.. but the actual doing of it.. well, lets just say I’ll need a week to recover from the last few weeks.. and a massage.. probably a pedicure and another massage! Since we made the actual decision to do this we have run to meetings with accountants, financial planners, realtors back to financial planners, holding garage sales, working, life in general and then this and then that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something Changed</title>
      <link>/articles/something-changed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 18:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/something-changed/</guid>
      <description>Something changed this year and it’s a good thing. Over the years, usually while on vacation, Paul and I have talked about travelling, getting out of the rat race and like most people, usually done it in “pipe-dream” mode. We’d met people who were travelling for several years, people who downsized so they could travel for half the year, who just made life changes to make it happen and we’d think “we should do this”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arcteryx Bora 65</title>
      <link>/articles/arcteryx-bora-65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 08:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/arcteryx-bora-65/</guid>
      <description>Our Arc’Teryx Bora 65 Backpacks are 2 of the best things we’ve purchased. Despite the miles on them they’ve come through everything with flying colours. Arc’Teryx has provided us with some great products. They are located in Vancouver, Canada and produce very high quality gear that they completely stand behind. Over the years we’ve had 3 backpacks (Bora 80 and 2 Bora 65’s), 4 Gore-Tex jackets (1 15-year-old and 3 newish Theta ARs) and 2 hooded Atom LT insulated jackets from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to get in touch, you can send us an email with the following form. Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>