<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Packs on Carry On Round The World</title>
    <link>/packs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Packs on Carry On Round The World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 20:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/packs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s Travel Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/paulspack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 20:41:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/paulspack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what is in Paul&amp;rsquo;s pack for travel. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see his Pacific Crest Trail load out here and his Annapurna Circuit load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen&#39;s Travel Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/helenspack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 10:41:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/helenspack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what is in Helen&amp;rsquo;s pack for travel. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see her Pacific Crest Trail load out here and her Annapurna Circuit load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen&#39;s PCT Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/helens-pct-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:44:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/helens-pct-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Helen&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Pacific Crest Trail. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see her travel load out here and her Annapurna Circuit load out here.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s PCT Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/pauls-pct-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:44:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/pauls-pct-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Paul&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Pacific Crest Trail. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see his travel load out here and his Annapurna Circuit load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helen&#39;s Annapurna Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/helens-annapurna-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/helens-annapurna-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Helen&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Annapurna Circuit treks. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see her travel load out here and her PCT load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul&#39;s Annapurna Pack</title>
      <link>/packs/pauls-annapurna-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 16:43:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/packs/pauls-annapurna-pack/</guid>
      <description>This page shows what was in Paul&amp;rsquo;s pack for the Annapurna Circuit treks. It is generated using lighterpack.com which is a great way to organize your packing lists for various activities. You can see his travel load out here and his PCT load out here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>