<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Carry On Round The World</title>
    <link>/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Carry On Round The World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 15:53:22 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We Quit</title>
      <link>/articles/we-quit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 15:53:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/we-quit/</guid>
      <description>We quit! Yep, we quit our jobs! February 9th, 2017 is our last day. Paul gave notice just before Christmas and I told my boss on Friday the 13th! The humour of that, while lost on some people, was not lost on me and I will admit to a giggle about it. Luckily our coworkers are very excited for us and have been great. For both of us the build up to quitting was bigger than the reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision Made Tickets Booked</title>
      <link>/articles/decision-made-tickets-booked/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 16:31:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/decision-made-tickets-booked/</guid>
      <description>Decision Made! What? When did this happen? I know it’s been a while since I took the time to write out something about our plans. Partially because we have been super busy and some things took much longer then expected so we weren’t sure what was happening. We also had some changes in the family that had us questioning our decisions. The quick catch up:
 June – accepted offer on the house, Paul ruptured his Achilles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planning Our Rtw Route</title>
      <link>/articles/planning-our-rtw-route/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 16:05:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/planning-our-rtw-route/</guid>
      <description>So far we’ve come up with this list of countries we’d like to see. I’m sure it will morph over time but it’s a good starting point. Planning our RTW route started out as what seemed like a massively important and overwhelming decision. After much research and brain racking we came to the conclusion that for us, it really didn’t need to be. We decided to start in Thailand, in SE Asia as we’ve been there many times and it’d let us get our traveling legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a Pack</title>
      <link>/articles/choosing-a-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 17:12:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/choosing-a-pack/</guid>
      <description>Expect The Unexpected Choosing a travel pack is a major decision when traveling. The wrong choice can have a big impact on a trip. Dragging a roller through sand to your beach side bungalow, carrying a duffel bag by its single carry strap for half an hour through a city or seeing your backpack come up the luggage carousel ramp with one of its shoulder straps torn off is no fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airline Carry on Rules</title>
      <link>/articles/airline-carry-on-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 17:51:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/airline-carry-on-rules/</guid>
      <description>Airline carry on rules can vary wildly. They each have their own specific guidelines for items that you can bring on-board a flight. Some even allow for a secondary “personal item” like a purse or laptop bag. If you do your research you’ll find lots of people saying a 45 L pack is good for carry on. As you’ll find out, this is not always the case. If you aren’t exactly within an airline’s requirements it’ll come down to the whim of the staff working on the day of your flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definition of Home</title>
      <link>/articles/definition-of-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 19:03:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/definition-of-home/</guid>
      <description>What’s the definition of home? It sounds simple doesn’t it but I’m not sure that it is. I was born in Liverpool, England, Helen was born in Belfast, Northern Ireland. We both moved to Canada with our families. Helen at the young age of 4 and myself at 13. Years later we met in Saskatchewan in 1991 and since then have spent our last 23 years living our adult lives together in Calgary, Alberta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carry on Only</title>
      <link>/articles/carry-on-only/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 16:41:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/carry-on-only/</guid>
      <description>28 days later and we are back! It wasn’t years on the road but it was a good test of living out of our new Gregory 38 L and 40 L bags (J38 and Z40). The traveling with carry on only experiment was definitely a success. It sure was liberating being able to walk off the plane with all our possessions on our backs. We flew Air Canada, Thai Airways International and the regional Thai Smile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moments of November Oddness</title>
      <link>/articles/moments-of-november-oddness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 17:59:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/moments-of-november-oddness/</guid>
      <description>Is oddness a word? Since it didn’t come up underlined I can only assume yes, I could confirm that it is.. but where is the fun in that? I like the start so will just go with it. November has been full of odd moments. It all started off when I booked a massage… sounds scary I know! It appears that the booking of the massage has resulted in me losing my job, being diagnosed with Celiac Disease, my family together for the first time in 17 years, a new hot water tank and swimming lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gear Conundrum</title>
      <link>/articles/the-gear-conundrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 18:10:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/the-gear-conundrum/</guid>
      <description>Winter is coming… no really it is supposed to snow. Thankfully we have restored the garage to its intended use and our vehicles are parked indoors so we won’t need to get our the ice scraper in the morning. After a recent work trip to Chicago by me, we were able to update our countries with carry on only to include the US. I have to admit I was somewhat nervous about doing carry on with just me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling Everything to Travel</title>
      <link>/articles/selling-everything-to-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 18:26:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/selling-everything-to-travel/</guid>
      <description>What!?! This was supposed to be easy.. sell everything and travel. Sure.. but the actual doing of it.. well, lets just say I’ll need a week to recover from the last few weeks.. and a massage.. probably a pedicure and another massage! Since we made the actual decision to do this we have run to meetings with accountants, financial planners, realtors back to financial planners, holding garage sales, working, life in general and then this and then that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something Changed</title>
      <link>/articles/something-changed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 18:56:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/something-changed/</guid>
      <description>Something changed this year and it’s a good thing. Over the years, usually while on vacation, Paul and I have talked about travelling, getting out of the rat race and like most people, usually done it in “pipe-dream” mode. We’d met people who were travelling for several years, people who downsized so they could travel for half the year, who just made life changes to make it happen and we’d think “we should do this”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arcteryx Bora 65</title>
      <link>/articles/arcteryx-bora-65/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 08:15:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/arcteryx-bora-65/</guid>
      <description>Our Arc’Teryx Bora 65 Backpacks are 2 of the best things we’ve purchased. Despite the miles on them they’ve come through everything with flying colours. Arc’Teryx has provided us with some great products. They are located in Vancouver, Canada and produce very high quality gear that they completely stand behind. Over the years we’ve had 3 backpacks (Bora 80 and 2 Bora 65’s), 4 Gore-Tex jackets (1 15-year-old and 3 newish Theta ARs) and 2 hooded Atom LT insulated jackets from them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>