<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Van Life on Carry On Round The World</title>
    <link>/van-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Van Life on Carry On Round The World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 20:35:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/van-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Headliner and Thinsulate</title>
      <link>/van-life/headliner-and-thinsulate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 10:28:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/headliner-and-thinsulate/</guid>
      <description>Removing the headliner makes insulating above a breeze. All you need for tools are an 7mm socket and a set of trim removal tools like this. With the following steps it only took about 10 minutes to remove and same to re-install.
  Pop out the 3 orange clips holding up the rear center of the headliner.
  Pry out and put aside 2 plastic trays in center of headliner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roof Fan Installation</title>
      <link>/van-life/roof-fan-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 10:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/roof-fan-installation/</guid>
      <description>A big right of passage when DIY&amp;rsquo;ing a van is the roof fan installation. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing like cutting a gaping hole in a brand new van. No pressure! :) I highly recommend you pick up a decent metal jigsaw blade. I believe the one I used was 25 teeth per inch and it cut the sheet metal like butter even with an old jigsaw. I also recommend watching as many YouTube videos as you can stomach on this as there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of good ideas (and what not to do) out there, they&amp;rsquo;re just spread out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sound Deadener and Flooring</title>
      <link>/van-life/sound-deadener-and-flooring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 10:27:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/sound-deadener-and-flooring/</guid>
      <description>The first thing we did to our new van was to add some Noico sound deadener to the metal panels. This stops a lot of the resonance that the larger panel sections are pron to and drastically reduces noise. We ordered 2 boxes of the 80 mil 36 sqft Noico and it worked out almost perfectly to do the walls, ceiling, above the front headliner, inside the side and rear door panels and inside the passenger seat pedestal (to help with noise from our Chinese diesel heater).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parking Pad</title>
      <link>/van-life/parking-pad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 10:22:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/parking-pad/</guid>
      <description>Paul&amp;rsquo;s parents have graciously offered to let us park the van at the side of their house when its not in use as we are off travelling. There was tons of room for the van and it is nicely sheltered between 2 houses. The first time we parked it there it spun out a lot as the pebbles are quite large and round making them like ball bearings. Rather than digging holes with spinning wheels and having to fill them in every time we come and go we decided to make a better parking pad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Diesel Heater</title>
      <link>/van-life/chinese-diesel-heater/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 10:28:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/van-life/chinese-diesel-heater/</guid>
      <description>Every Canadian Van build needs a heater at some point. We&amp;rsquo;ve been camping in the Rockies in July and August and it has snowed. After looking at all of the solutions to the heat problem, one stood out: Chinese Diesel Heaters. They are by far and away the leader in price/performance, mostly due to the exorbitant costs $1000USD+ of brand name gas, propane and diesel heaters. Our transit has a gas fuel tank already but for several hundred dollars savings we are willing to add a small diesel tank.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>